SecureVPN - Privacy Policy
==========================

This Website(SecureVPN.com), its owners (collectively,) and constituents believe that the privacy and security of our visitors and clients information are of utmost importance. As such, we administer strict policies safeguarding your privacy and security. This document ('Privacy Policy') defines and informs you of any and all of the instances in which your data and information (collectively, 'info') may be saved and how it may be used.

NOTE TO KIDS : SecureVPN IS NOT AVAILABLE TO PERSONS UNDER THE AGE OF 18. If you are under 18 years of age, please do not use SecureVPN.

INFO WE COLLECT

From Clients of our Service:

* \-Payment data.
    
* \-E-mail Address.
    
* \-User account and technical identifiers.

From the Website and E-mail:

* \-Submissions on the 'Contact Us' page.
    
* \-Any e-mails we receive.
    
* \-Clients who opt to use the optional control panel will receive a temporary cookie.

INFO USES:

* \-E-mail address is used to send subscription information and payment confirmations only.
    
* \-Payment data and account/technical identifiers are used to manage client signups, payments, and cancellations.
    
* \-Contact submissions and e-mails will be used for correspondence.
    
* \-Temporary cookies are used to handle control panel logins.

SecureVPN.com does not collect or log any traffic of its Virtual Private Network ("VPN") service.

DISCLOSURE

SecureVPN encrypts every page visited by our Users, thus protecting communications between each User and the Internet. SecureVPN employs certain physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of any information collected. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant that the safeguards will be uninterrupted or effective, or that any information you transmit to SecureVPN will remain secure, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, SecureVPN employs certain techniques and technologies to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. Please note that SecureVPN helps secure your Internet session, not your computer. SecureVPN software does not protect your computer from viruses or malware. We recommend getting anti-virus/anti-malware solutions from one of our reputable partners in order to also help secure your computer. SecureVPN.com is a business that strives to protect privacy and the privacy rights of our clients. We may disclose information to governmental authorities or agencies, including law enforcement agencies, at their request or pursuant to a court order, subpoena or other legal process, if there is a good faith belief that such collection or disclosure is required by law.

SecureVPN.com will not participate with any request that is unconstitutional.

SecureVPN does not share your private information with any third parties aside from the disclosures already made in this privacy policy.

BY USING THIS WEBSITE AND/OR SERVICES, YOU AGREE THAT YOU CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND ANY CHANGES HERETO IN THE FUTURE. YOU AGREE THAT SecureVPN.com MAY MAKE CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME WITHOUT ANY GIVEN NOTICE AT ITS DISCRETION.
